The big men circle in
the center of the ring
here at the Olympic Auditorium.
The crowd is agog.
They want The
Annihilator to lose.
Sailor Jack in the
blue trunks takes a shot
to the pit of the stomach
from the foot of
The Annihilator.
The Annihilator,
with an arm hold,
throws him against
the ropes and hits him
under the Adam's
apple with an elbow,
a vicious, hurting blow.
And here is a body
slam by The Annihilator.
Sailor Jack to the canvas
with The Annihilator
trying for the pin.
The count got to two
and Sailor Jack
kicked out of it.
Oh, that was close,
ladies and gentlemen.
He had a count of
two and one half.
That means, simply,
another half-second
he would've lost the
Global Association
championship title.
Yeah. Yeah, you got him.
Now, hold him.
Come on, Annihilator.
Kill him!
Fun, huh?
Come on, twist that sucker!
Kill him! Come on, Annihilator!
You can do it.
You don't come to these
things to make friends, do you?
These people don't
know The Annihilator. I do.
His name's Vic Garrett. Used
to be one of the good guys.
They called him Go-Go Garrett
until Sailor Jack
hurt him one night.
Sailor Jack always fights dirty.
Tell that to Sailor Jack.
Get him, Sailor.
His arm!
Come on, ref, that's a foul.
Come on, big guy!
All right, one shot. Cut it out.
Kill him, Sailor.
One, two, three.
Well, the better man won,
as the crowd seems
to think so too.
We're going to have
a word with Sailor Jack
as he makes his way
to the locker room.
It was quite a fight
out there tonight.
The Annihilator
was very, very good.
Hey, Sailor Jack.
How about a word
for our TV audience?
Yeah. Once the champ,
always the champ.
What's this I hear about
you jumping ship, Sailor?
Rumor has it that you're going
over to the Federal Association.
Like you said,
it's only a rumor.
What's the matter with you?
Figure you didn't do enough
damage two years ago?
You know, you're a bad
loser and a worse wrestler,
you know that?
Get him out of here.
Hurry up. Vic, please.
Do you mean to tell me you
want to get right back into the ring
with Sailor Jack?
Are you kiddin'?
I'll kill him. I
swear it. I'll kill him.
Vic, we've gotta
take care of your arm.
Folks, in case Sailor Jack
does jump associations,
there cannot be a rematch.
Tommy O'Keefe is here.
He heads up the
Global Association.
Any truth to this rumor?
Absolutely, positively
none. Thank you very much.
I'm going over to his place
tonight and let him have it.
He didn't mean to hurt you, Vic.
Yeah. Take it easy, Vic.
You know Sailor. He
just got carried away.
Okay, people. Let's
close the store, huh?
Let me take care
of the kid, please?
Huh, Gentleman George?
Sleep on it. See
you tomorrow, Vic.
How bad is it?
Well, it's nothing that a
little hydrotherapy won't cure.
Rotate it.
What a mess.
Don't dwell on it, Vic.
Who am I kidding, Bobby?
I'm getting too old
for this. It's no good.
Well, you won't get an
argument from me on that, pal.
You could've argued a little.
Hey, you weren't serious about
going after Sailor, were you?
Yeah, I was. Sort of.
But what's the point?
You know, Sailor and me
used to be good friends,
but that was messed
up somewhere.
Maybe we oughta talk it out,
just Sailor and me.
Hey, hold it right there.
Who is it you're here to see?
Jack Saunders.
Not so fast, pal.
Yeah, get me the police.
Sailor?
Don't move. Just
hold it right there.
Uh, Ben?
Yeah?
What are you doing?
Tryin' to fix my chair.
Oh. Well, can I help you?
No, I'll get it.
Uh, Ben?
You know how sometimes
you take on a new client
because the case interests you
or you think an
injustice has been done
and the person is innocent?
Yeah.
Well, those are all
real good reasons.
I think so.
And sometimes
you take on a client
because somebody
asks you to, don't you?
Sometimes.
If I asked you to, would you?
What are you talking about?
Well, we have a new
might-be client. Maybe.
I mean, Michelle's
bailing him out
down at the jail.
Michelle's bailing
him out for what?
Murder.
Who is this person?
It's Vic Garrett.
Friend of yours?
Well, not exactly.
I mean, I know him.
Well, I mean, I know who he is.
Uh, he's a
professional wrestler.
Cassie, you know my
opinion of these buffoons
you find so entertaining.
Ben, they're finely-tuned
professional athletes.
But these wrestlers
don't wrestle.
It's vaudeville, bad vaudeville.
One pratfall after another.
Ben.
They're nothing but clowns
lurching around
in these costumes
about the size of their IQs.
They're nothing but
a bunch of gorillas
that look like they escaped
from a hormone farm.
Ben.
This is The Annihilator.
Vic Garrett.
Well, hell, any friend of
Cassie's is a friend of mine.
Hello.
Uh, this is Ben
Matlock, an attorney,
and this is our
client, Vic Garrett.
Yeah.
I understand you tried to
keep Mr. Garrett from going up
to see Mr. Saunders last night.
Yeah, that's right.
Sailor had phoned down
earlier in the evening,
and he described him to me.
Said if he showed
not to let him up,
and if there was
trouble, call the police.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Thanks.
Uh, w-why don't you see
if we can get something
out of the paparazzi out there?
Okay.
Any idea how Sailor Jack knew
you were coming here last night?
His manager, Connie
Hammond. She must've told him.
She was in my dressing room
when I was shooting my mouth off
about getting even.
Who else was there?
My manager, Bobby Devine,
Tommy O'Keefe, head of the
Global Wrestling Association,
and a pro-wrestling friend of
mine named Gentleman George.
I'll tell you one thing:
If you were framed,
whoever did it had to know
you were coming
up here last night.
You can forget about Bobby.
He'd give his life for me.
Yeah. Like a freight
train went through here.
This is the way it
looked when I walked in.
Huh. Was anybody in
the corridor out there?
I didn't see anybody.
Was the door ajar or open or...?
I thought it was closed,
but when I banged on it,
it swung open.
Then what happened?
Well, I stood here
looking around.
Then I saw the wall over here,
came around and found Sailor.
Did you touch anything?
Just him when I was
feeling for a pulse.
The police report said you had
a cut on your hand. Let's see.
Yeah. I did that when
I was kneeling down.
It said you had red
wine on your pants.
Like I said, I kneeled down.
There was wine
all over the floor.
Said you have
these bruises all over.
I was just in a
championship match.
Hey, I didn't do it. You
make it sound like I did.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just a bad habit.
Boy, Sailor Jack must've
been in great shape.
I guess so. He did
a number on me.
Oh. Just look at this equipment.
Oh, sauna.
What are you doing here?
How dare you come back here.
I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
Uh, I'm Ben
Matlock, Vic's lawyer.
You were Sailor Jack's
manager, Connie Hammond, right?
That's right.
Could I ask you a few questions?
I don't think Sailor
would've approved of me
talking to his
murderer's lawyer.
Well, I, uh... I hate
to get technical,
but this is the scene
of the crime, and we...
We have a right to be here,
and we have to talk,
uh, here or
anywhere, uh, in court.
Okay. Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lose my temper,
but Sailor and I
were very close.
What do you wanna know?
Are you the one who told Sailor
that Vic might come up here
and confront him that night?
I warned him, yes.
For all the good it did.
And when was that?
On our way over here, I guess.
Oh, you came up
here that night too.
Yes. I came home
with him after the match.
How long did you stay?
A half-hour, 45 minutes.
We discussed some
business, and then I went home.
Did you talk about
his possible move
to the other
wrestling association?
Yes. As a matter
of fact, we did.
Were you for it or against it?
I was for anything that
would make us more money.
Huh.
The coroner said he was
killed between 10:30 and 11.
I was at Chez Robert's,
having dinner with some friends.
Roughly 30 waiters,
wine stewards
and fellow diners
can attest to that.
Does that answer your question?
Oh, yeah. More than answers it.
Mr. Matlock, why are you
treating me like a suspect?
Sailor Jack was my meal ticket.
Why on earth would
I wanna kill him?
Beats me.
Thank you for your time.
Oh. Those paparazzi
gave you some pictures?
Yeah. Some of them that
were outside Sailor's place
the night of the murder.
They didn't wanna
give me anything at first.
Yeah.
So I told them how
they might be able
to help convict the real killer
and how much you
would appreciate it
and how it would be
the right thing to do.
Yeah.
Then I gave them some money.
Good.
So, uh, these are the
pictures of who went in and out
the night of the murder.
Good morning.
Morning.
Now, there...
There's a picture
of Connie Hammond
going in with Sailor.
And a picture of Connie
Hammond coming out.
A couple of Japanese guys.
Pictures of other paparazzi.
Other than that, I don't
recognize anybody.
Tyler, how about going
down to the auditorium?
No.
Say what?
Ben, the people
down there are big.
I mean real big. They
are too big for me.
Forget it.
I'm not asking you
to wrestle anybody.
I just want you to go down there
and talk with Tommy O'Keefe.
He's the head of the
wrestling association here.
The man is wacko.
I just want you
to talk with him.
Sailor was gonna leave him
and fight for somebody else.
See how he feels about it.
He's not in any
of those pictures.
Maybe nobody took his picture.
Maybe he walked in backwards.
You know what's gonna happen.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Will you go down
there and talk with him?
Ben, Julie March
wants to see you.
Oh, okay.
Um, so, Ben, what do
you think of Vic's chances?
I should be back about 2.
Thank you very much.
Well, Connie Hammond's
alibi checks out.
Michelle, what do you
think of Vic's chances?
Of being convicted?
Yeah.
Very high.
Do you think he did it?
Well,
certainly all the evidence
seems to point that way.
However, that's not to say...
You think he did it.
Yes, but it's our
job to defend him.
Yeah, right.
Uh, thanks.
Anyone see you come in?
No. Get in here.
Oh, I guess this isn't
the will-call office.
Mr. O'Keefe.
He was listenin'
in at your door.
Hey, how about a little help?!
He go that way.
Fan out and find him.
There he is.
Who are you?
Ha-ha. Tyler Hudson.
I, uh, work for Ben Matlock.
He's the lawyer that's
defending Vic Garrett.
So, what are you doin' here?
Looking for suspects.
Like who? Like me?
I'd rather not say.
I'll tell you one thing.
I don't think Vic did it.
He didn't have it in him.
That Connie Hammond,
that's another matter.
She was here the other
day looking to invest 50 grand
in another wrestler.
Fifty grand?
Yep. Sailor Jack paid
her off and kicked her out.
That's where she got it.
That's why she killed him,
because he dumped her.
Look, she says she
was in another place
at the time of the murder.
Where were you?
Why would I kill Sailor
Jack? He's my star.
Yeah, but he was
gonna leave you.
You would've had to
replace him anyway.
Replace him?
Replace Sailor Jack?
You don't understand.
Wrestling is theater. Every
match is a morality play.
A battle between good
and evil and villains,
and Jack was a hero.
Every man and
woman in this country
who paid the price of admission
completely identified with him.
He stomped the vicious.
He wiped out the criminals.
He killed the terrorists.
He wasn't a wrestler.
He was America.
Replace him?
That oughta take me a
couple of years at least.
Get rid of him.
Come on in, Ben.
How'd you know it was me?
I always know when it's you.
Besides, a good criminal lawyer
never keeps a
prosecutor waiting.
Oh, yeah.
How's your day?
Oh, fine. Yours? Great.
Is this new?
No, it's old.
I got it at a rummage
sale in Athens.
The Athens in Georgia.
Oh, yeah.
It's not comfortable, is it?
Not much.
Well, it keeps unwanted
visits short and sweet.
Oh.
Here. Oh, yeah, thanks.
You know, this case
seems pretty one-sided,
so if you wanna
cut a deal, I'll listen.
I thought this meeting was
about the Vic Garrett case.
It is.
Well, aren't you overplaying
your hand a little?
Overplaying my hand?
Well, yeah, Julie, I... I...
I know that Vic
made some threats
and went over to Sailor's
apartment that night
and was seen
leaning over the body,
but all of that's
circumstantial.
Oh. You haven't heard?
Heard what?
Ben, I'm really sorry.
The investigator was supposed
to have notified you immediately.
Notified me?
They have an eyewitness.
In fact, she was
just here in my office.
She saw your client kill
Jack Saunders that night.
I'm really s... They
should have notified you.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Uh, I'm Ben Matlock,
Vic Garrett's lawyer.
I wonder if you could answer
some questions for me.
My pleasure.
Oh, good.
Do you mind if I
lift while we talk?
Oh, of course, of course.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Um... Um,
I understand the other
night after the match
you heard Vic say he was
gonna go over to Sailor Jack's
and have it out with him.
Look, I wanted to
help Vic, not hurt him.
Oh, I know it. I-I know it. I...
I understand you volunteered
to get even with
Sailor Jack for him.
Ungh. Well, maybe
Sailor had it comin'.
So did you?
Did I what?
Get even with him.
Never got the chance.
Where'd you go after the match?
What if I don't
feel like sayin'?
Well, I'd have to assume
you have something to hide.
How good are you assuming stuff
with your left foot
in your right ear?
You see, it seems to
me you had good reason
to want to hurt Sailor Jack.
How about I staple
your lip to your nose?
If he jumped to your league,
he'd be the champ 'cause
he'd be the good guy.
And all those Gentleman
George dolls and T-shirts
and comic books the
fans have been buying
would disappear
from the shelves.
You'd lose a fortune.
How about a little heart bypass?
I punch out your heart
and it bypasses your body.
Where were you at
the time of the murder?
Me and Vladimir were
at a poetry reading
at the Willow Springs
Institute of Fine Arts.
Willow Springs
Institute of Fine Arts?
Yes. I was reading a poem. Mine.
If you'll excuse me.
Hi, are you Michelle?
Donna Clifford?
Ready to take a little hike?
Yeah. How could you see
what was going on
in that apartment?
It's on the fourth floor.
Let's take the hike.
Didn't figure I'd be
seeing you again.
This'll be the last time. I
just came to get my stuff.
Goodbye and good riddance.
From right here,
you can see right into
the Sailor's living room.
It's still a wreck from
the fight the other night.
Are you sure it was
Vic Garrett you saw?
Absolutely it was him.
I know all the
bigtime wrestlers,
and I know what he
looks like without his mask.
Who else did you
see in his apartment?
Mostly that witch of a manager.
She used to come around a lot.
Always looked like
they were fighting.
Probably tryin' to run his life.
At least that's what
all the magazines say.
Anyone else?
Not really.
How long have you
been coming up here?
A couple months.
Since I found out
where the Sailor lived.
Sometimes I sleep up here.
Heh. I loved the Sailor.
I really, really did.
He was my whole life.
Bye, Sailor.
Hey, Vic.
Hi.
Uh, I never got a
chance to tell you
how much I love to
watch you wrestle.
Oh, thanks.
I don't like it when they
call you the bad guy.
As far as I'm concerned,
you are the good guy.
Thanks again.
I know you're really
worried about everything,
but you have the
best lawyer there is,
and everything's gonna work out.
I hope. How's my case look?
Oh, it's coming along.
It... It's gonna
be fine, really.
Well, thanks for trying
to make me feel better.
Yes.
The cause of death was
a depressed skull fracture
causing a subdural hematoma,
which apparently occurred
when he fell forward,
his head striking the
corner of a coffee table
in his apartment.
Additional but non-fatal
bruises were also found
along the base of the neck,
apparently the result of
a blow from a blunt object
believed to be a wine bottle.
Death was instantaneous?
Yes.
And were you able to
determine the time of death?
Sometime between
10:30 and 11 p.m.
Thank you, Dr. Carlin.
No further questions.
Cross-examine, Mr. Matlock.
Not at this time, Your Honor.
Next witness.
Prosecution calls
Mr. Peter Lucas to the stand.
When I tried to stop him,
he grabs me by the
front of my jacket,
lifts me up in the air and
throws me out of the way.
What happened next, Mr. Lucas?
He went in the elevator.
I called the police.
Approximately
what time was that?
Ten-thirty, 10:40,
something like that.
Go on, Mr. Lucas.
Then the police showed up,
and I took 'em up to
Mr. Saunders' apartment.
Did you find anything?
The place was in a shambles.
Mr. Saunders was dead,
and he was leaning
over the body.
May the record reflect
that Mr. Lucas is
referring to the defendant.
Thank you. No further questions.
So noted.
Mr. Matlock?
No questions, Your Honor.
Okay. You can step
down. Next witness.
Prosecution calls
Miss Donna Clifford
to the stand.
Then I saw Sailor go
to the door and open it,
and all of a sudden, Vic Garrett
dove into the room on top of him
and started punching him,
and suddenly it
was a flat-out fight.
Chairs being knocked
over. Lamps breaking.
It was awful.
And the worst part
was when Vic Garrett
picked up a bottle of wine
and smashed it
over Sailor's head.
He fell face forward.
He was just lyin' there.
I was waitin' for him to move.
He never did. He was dead.
Thank you, Miss Clifford.
Nothing further.
Cross-examine.
You cared a great deal
for Sailor Jack, didn't you?
I loved him.
Well, I know that sounds
childish and dumb,
but I swear it's true.
Is that why you were
up on that rooftop
day in and day out,
because you were
watching over him?
That's exactly it.
I was just kinda
trying to protect him.
So, what did you do when
you saw he was dead?
Call the police?
No. Well, they
were already there.
Did you go over and tell
them what you'd seen?
No. I was in shock, I guess.
I just sort of sat there
for about ten minutes.
And what did you
do after ten minutes?
I went home and went to bed.
Hm. Like I said, I
was sorta numb.
About what time did you
go up on the roof that night?
About 9:30 or so.
And what time did you leave?
About 11.
Could you remove one of
those sandals you're wearing
and hold it up for
the court, please?
Looks like they've
seen a lot of use.
I wear 'em every day.
They made a pretty
distinctive sound
on the metal fire
escape on the building
across from Sailor
Jack's, didn't they?
I guess so.
Ooh. Don't you think
they were pretty loud?
So loud that
I'd bet if we brought
Mrs. Kowalski into court...
The woman who
lives in the building.
I bet she'd testify
she heard you
the night of the murder.
Only she'd say she
heard you around midnight,
which is when you
went up those stairs,
and at 7 the next morning
when you came back down again.
Donna, isn't that
what she'd say?
Yeah.
You didn't know Sailor was dead.
You didn't find
out till the next day.
You made up the
whole story, didn't you?
I had to do
something. I loved him.
I just wanted the guy
who killed him to pay for it.
We all want whoever
did it punished, Donna.
It's just terribly important
we get the right person.
Ah, Ben, I got somebody
I'd like you to meet.
This is Sammy and Jimmy Ito.
Hello.
These are the gentlemen
that were in the photos.
They were standing around
outside Sailor Jack's apartment
the night he was murdered.
Oh.
What were they doing
outside Sailor's apartment?
Casing the joint
for Tommy O'Keefe.
He brought 'em
in to lean on Sailor
to keep him from
jumping associations.
They were gonna
lean on Sailor. Mm-hm.
How were they gonna do that?
What was that?
Well, it was a table.
What are they doing here?
They work for us now. I
made 'em a better offer.
Better offer?
More money.
Uh... Heh.
Did they see Gentleman George
go in Sailor's
building that night?
No.
Did they see Tommy O'Keefe?
They didn't. Mm-mm.
They didn't see anybody go in?
No.
Well, we know what this means.
All of our suspects have alibis.
I guess nobody
committed this murder.
That's right.
Your services will
no longer be required.
Well, I guess we're nowhere.
Gentleman George.
George's alibi checks out.
Connie Hammond.
Her alibi checks out.
The Ito brothers.
The Ito brothers swear
that Tommy O'Keefe
didn't go in Sailor's
apartment building that night.
Well, to quote a
great legal mind,
what we need is a bright idea,
or else maybe it
was The Annihilator.
No. No, Vic wouldn't do it.
He couldn't. I know it.
Cassie, there is no one else.
You know what
our problem's been?
We didn't listen.
Somebody's been talking to us,
telling us the same
thing over and over again,
but we refused to listen.
Take a look at these.
Take a good look.
Oh, right.
Ben?
I'm in the sauna.
I-I got it.
I have too.
Uh, Dr. Carlin,
uh, I'd like you to
clarify something for me.
You testified earlier that
Sailor Jack Saunders died
that night sometime
between 10:30 and 11.
That's right.
Would you please tell the court
how you arrived at
that particular time?
One of the principal
determinants
of a time of death
is body temperature.
Uh, 98.6 is the norm, of course,
and there's a
fairly reliable scale
by which it falls after death.
Were you at all influenced
by the physical details,
the fact that the
police found Vic Garrett
leaning over the body
at approximately 10:45?
Of course, but such factors
serve mainly to confirm what
the physiological evidence
had already led me to believe.
Well, what about this?
Well, what if just
prior to death,
Sailor Jack's body temperature
had been artificially raised?
Uh, maybe he had been exercising
or he was in a hot
room or a sauna?
Would your computations
still hold true?
Well, no. They'd
be completely off.
It would've taken much longer
for the body
temperature to fall.
So under those circumstances,
your time of death
could be off by an hour?
Or more.
Thank you, doctor.
I have no questions, Your Honor.
You can step down.
Next witness, Mr. Matlock.
Ms. Connie Hammond.
Did you attend a wrestling match
between Jack
Saunders and Vic Garrett
on the evening of the 18th?
Of course. I was present
for all Jack's matches.
I was his manager.
Well, did you go back to
Vic Garrett's dressing room
after the match?
Yes. Things got a
little rough in the ring.
I wanted to make
sure Vic was okay.
Did you hear Vic Garrett
threaten to go over to
your client's apartment
later that night and kill him?
Yes.
What did you do?
I warned Jack, and he, in turn,
alerted the security guard
in his apartment building.
Did you go to his
apartment that night?
Yes.
What did you do?
We talked.
What time did you leave?
Around 9, 9:15.
Actually, I knew
that, because...
that's approximately when
this photograph was taken.
Actually, there are
two photographs.
This is a photograph of you
entering the building
with Sailor Jack.
Let's call that
defendant's exhibit E.
And this is a photograph of
you leaving the building alone.
Let's call that
defendant's exhibit F.
Now, these are
photographs of you
entering and
leaving the building
the night of the
murder, are they not?
I suppose, but there
were a lot of photographers
around that night.
That's right. There
were. That's right.
Now, tell me this:
Why was your hair curly
in this picture, like it is now,
and straight in this one?
Um, Jack and I took a sauna.
My hair always goes
straight like that after a sauna.
Oh.
Heh.
We're both adults.
It's hardly a big deal.
Oh, that's okay. That's okay.
But the medical examiner,
uh, has just told us
that if Jack Saunders
took a sauna
just before he died,
it would've elevated
his body temperature.
He could've been killed
long before we
previously believed.
You just destroyed
your own alibi.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I believe that's true.
I believe you didn't know
that his taking a sauna
would elevate his
body temperature
and almost work in your favor.
I think it was
simpler than that.
I think, during an argument,
you hit him in the head
with that bottle of wine
and killed him,
and then decided to make it look
like a huge brawl
had taken place.
And since Vic Garrett
had already threatened him,
everybody would
just naturally assume
that he had killed him.
These are ridiculous
accusations.
And pure speculation. I object.
Your Honor,
I have two more items I'd
like to enter into evidence.
Proceed, Mr. Matlock.
The first... is a
still photograph
made from a videotape.
Let's call this one
defendant's exhibit G.
Do you recognize yourself
standing next to Jack Saunders
when he was being
interviewed after the match
the night of the murder?
Yes.
This is the same dress
that you were wearing
when you entered the building
and when you left, is it not?
Yes.
It's a pretty dress.
It looks expensive.
It's very expensive.
It's an original.
I imagine that's why...
you took it to
Barrington Cleaners
instead of throwing it out.
Let's call this
defendant's exhibit H.
This is the dress,
isn't it, Connie?
I suppose.
And I suppose that's why
you took it back after
they didn't get it cleaned
the first time.
Care to tell us
how it got soiled?
When you hit Jack
Saunders with that bottle,
red wine splattered everywhere.
And red wine, once it's set,
they can't get it out.
Your Honor, move for dismissal.
Ms. March?
State concurs.
Case dismissed.
Take him. Come on, Annihilator.
Come on, get him!
Come on, Vic.
Come on, now! Yeah, okay.
Ben, it was really nice of
you to come down here.
Well, it's his last
fight and everything.
I think Vic really
appreciates it.
Well...
Wait a minute.
He's fightin' dirty.
Hey, wait a minute!
Hey, Vic, get out of
there. Get out of there.
Get out of there.
Pound him. Twist him. Throw
him. Throw him. Throw him.
Get your legs around him.
Kill the son of a...!
www.tvsubtitles.net